CHRISTY MADILAO

BUSINESS TECHNOLOGY MANAGEMENT STUDENT

+1(778)994-9816 | CHRISTYMADILAO7@GMAIL.COM | CHRISTY-MADILAO.GETFORGE.IO/

|LINKEDIN.COM/IN/CHRISTYMADILAO/ | 2075 WEST MALL, VANCOUVER V6T1Z2

PROFILE

Fourth-year Sauder School of Business BCom student with numerous experience working in challenging and fast-paced work environments. Currently specializing in Business Technology Management with Business Analytics concentration, given excellent analytical skills and interest in technology. Proactive self-starter with excellent organizational and prioritization skills. Proven ability to work well in diverse teams and independently, adapting to unexpected situations and multi-task several responsibilities. Excellent communication and relationship-building skills through previous customer-facing roles. Strong desire to learn from respectable colleagues and gain new skills. Strong attention to detail, ability to think out of the box and proven problem-solving skills.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Python
- Tableau
- HTML
- R Studio
- JavaScript
- Excel
- CSS
- PowerPoint

EDUCATION

University of British Columbia

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE | EXPECTED GRADUATION: MAY 2020

- Specialization: Business Technology Management, Business Analytics Concentration
- Current Cumulative Average: 82.9%, Dean's Honor Roll Status
- · Key Courses:
 - o Management of Information System, 90%
 - o Information Systems Analysis & Design, 88%
 - o Business Programming & Analytics, 85%
- Scholarships:
 - o William & Ada Isabelle Steel Scholarship
 - o Morrow Scholarship in Commerce
- · Activities & Societies:
 - o Treasurer & Sponsorship Coordinator at University Fashion Club
 - Tax Volunteer at UBC Tax Assistance Clinic for Students
 - Ambassador at National Strategic Consulting Competition & Conference
 - o Campus Program Presenter at Commerce Undergraduate Society

EXPERIENCE

Canaccord Learning Commons Student Assistant

SAUDER SCHOOL OF BUSINESS | AUG 2018 - PRESENT

- Facilitate equipment borrowing process and quickly comprehend new concepts and technologies to provide patrons with excellent service
- Revised and improved training program for incoming student assistants to provide better knowledge of business processes at learning commons
- Assisted in creation of marketing and social media content to increase social online presence of learning commons

Business Administrative & Accounting Assistant Intern

CENTRE DISTRIBUTION | MAY 2019 - AUG 2019

- Displayed strong understanding of database management systems by managing customer information and payment processes via Net Suite and other SaaS platforms
- Showcased attention to detail by monitoring client's payment cycles and providing weekly account updates to improve stakeholder relations
- Worked effectively in teams by communicating with different departments and deployed new business processes to improve company's logistical and accounting strategy
- Collaborated with accounting manager to better manage invoice discrepancies by revising preexisting online form and allow clients to navigate the form more easily

Python Instructor Volunteer

THE C.O.D.E INITIATIVE | JUN 2019 - JUL 2019

- Worked with children with Autism Spectrum Disorder (ASD) to pursue their passion in coding by introducing basic Python commands and syntax with the use of platform Tynker
- Effectively guided students through course material by demonstrating patience, interpersonal skills and adjusting teaching methods based on student's individual needs

Sales Specialist

PANDORA | JUN 2018 - APR 2019

- Achieved top sales performance (top 5% consistently) among associates by demonstrating clear and effective communication in multiple languages and understanding of the Pandora customer value proposition
- Handled multiple customers during peak sales periods with a calm demeanor and high level of professionalism